siterobot.com 2015-03-30

# Privacy policy | Siterobot

Siterobot will not share the personal information that is secured by Siterobot users except the conditions which has been declared in **Terms &conditions and Privacy Policy**.

#### IP Adresses

Siterobot identifies IP addresses of users for finding out solutions to the problems, which user may have and about the system, quickly. IP addresses can as well be used to generally define the users and collect comprehensive demographic information.

#### Correction

Users declare their some personal information such as name, company identification,telephone, address, email) when they creating account. Siterobot may use declared information by the users, except the purposes and content defined in **Siterobot Terms &and conditions** such as marketing, statistical evaluation, composing a database with the other third parties.

Siterobot can provide links to the other websites. Siterobot has no responsibility for the privacy applications and contents of the websites accessed by such links. Personal information include the name, surname, address, telephone number, email address and all kinds of information to identify the user. Siterobot, except declared conditions in this Privacy Policy, will not reveal any of your personal information to the companies that are not in cooperation with Siterobot and to third parties. In the limited situations identified below, Siterobot can outside the provisions of this Privacy Policy reveal the user's information to third parties. Such limited number of situations are;

• To comply with the obligations arising from legal rules in force;

• To comply with the requirements of the Siterobot Terms and Conditions and other agreements between "Siterobot and the users and to put them into practice;

• In the event that information concerning the users is requested by government and courts for the purpose of duly executing an investigation or an enquiry;

• The situation in which providing information is needed for the protection of the user´s rights and security.

#### Cookies

Siterobot can obtain information about the users and usage habits of users in Siterobot. Usage of Siterobot by using a technical communication file **(Cookie)** as well. Such technical communication files are small text files send by a website to a users browser to be kept in the main memory. Technical communication file stores the conditions and choices about a website and eases the Internet usage. Technical communication file facilitates to provide statistical information concerning, how many people uses Siterobot, the purpose of the visit of a person of Siterobot, the number and duration of the visits; and to dynamically produce advertisements and content from user pages designed specifically for the users. Technical communication file is not designed to collect data or any other personal information from the main memory or your e-mail. Most of the browsers are initially designed to accept technical communication files but the users, if they wish, can change the settings so that no technical communication file is received or an alert would appear when a technical communication file is sent.

#### Others

Information requested by Siterobot from the users who reply to the periodical surveys on the Siterobot are used by Siterobot and persons in cooperation with Siterobot for the purposes of direct marketing to such users, statistical analyses and composition of a data base. Siterobot can amend the provisions of this **Privacy Policy** anytime by publishing the amendment on Siterobot. The amendments on the "Privacy Policy" become effective as they are published on Siterobot.
